<Document>
  # Introduction
  Welcome to Devilstation, a publically available fork of Impstation.
  
  Servers like ours need rules. We will treat you like you read the rules, even if you did not.
  
  Admins are allowed to remove players from the round at their own discretion, so long as it is for the sake of moderation purposes.
  
  If you feel like you were removed from the round for no reason, or you were never told why, please be sure to AHELP.
  
  [bold]Admins are held to the same standards as players are.[/bold]

  ## The Rules
  
  These rules apply at all times, including between rounds. If you believe someone is breaking these rules, or is acting suspicious, feel free to AHELP.
  
  - 0. You must be (and act) at least 16 years of age or older to play on the server.
  
  If you are found to be under this age threshold, you will be permanently banned, even if your birthday is in 5 minutes.
  
  - 1. No erotic content anywhere.
  
  This is a community that includes minors. Act like it.
  
  - 2. No slurs or derogatory content in any communication channels.
  
  This includes fictional slurs.
  
  - 3. Match the roleplay level of those around you.
  
  We are a MRP server, and as such expect you to play a character at all times.
  
  You don't have to be perfect. You can mispell things. You can have bad grammar. Just act like a realistic character.
  
  - 4. Play antagonists responsibly.
  
  As most servers expect, murderboning and non-target killing is disallowed, unless you have Die a Glorious Death, you are an animal antagonist (i.e. Rat King or Dragon,) or you are a nuclear operative.
  
  - 5. Be courteous and understanding to other PLAYERS.
  
  People, just like you, will make mistakes. While this is not a rule outright banning being rude in-character, you must remember that everyone you are playing with is [bold]human[/bold], again, [bold]just like you[/bold].
  
  - 6. If your presence in the server is negatively impacting everyone elses rounds, regardless of a rule break, you will be removed.
  
  This is not a blanket rule meant to allow admins to ban anyone. If we can visibly see (or hear) your actions having a negative effect on EVERYONE ELSE, you are not playing the game to create a story.
  
  You're playing the game only for yourself, and that is not what we want here.
  
</Document>
